Guide to the Darlington Autograph Files, 1610-1914 DAR.1925.07
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Pieter Schuyler et al. to Albany, February 6, 1696/7 (Box 6, Folder 56)
- Charles Scott to Frederick Ridgeley, October 2, 1794 (Box 6, Folder 57)
- John Scott, Bond of Conveyance, July 30, 1827 (Box 6, Folder 58)
- John Scott to George W. Haller, Indenture, July 30, 1829 (Box 6, Folder 59)
- Benjamin Sebastian to William Croghan, June 22, 1802 (Box 6, Folder 60)
- George O. Seilhamer to Fred G. Berger, November 16, 1889 (Box 6, Folder 61)
- Antoine Selin to Edward Hand, March 14, 1779 (Box 6, Folder 62)
- Horatio Sharpe to Philip Sharpe, November 3, 1758 (Box 6, Folder 63)
- Horatio Sharpe to the commissioners of the paper currency office, June 3, 1762 (Box 6, Folder 64)
- Edward Shippen to William Bradford, February 26, 1765 (Box 6, Folder 65)
- William Shirley to Robert Hunter Morris, May 21, 1755 (Box 6, Folder 66)
- Peyton Short to William Croghan, August 4, 1824 (Box 6, Folder 67)
- Charles Simms, Bond signed by James O'Hara, February 15, 1777 (Box 6, Folder 68)
- J. S. Skinner to William Croghan Jr., August 18, 1827 (Box 6, Folder 69)
- Joshua Slocum, Souvenir booklet with piece of mainsail autographed by Slocum, 1901 (Box 6, Folder 70)
- Hester Smith to Hannah Penn, July 2, 1714 (Box 6, Folder 71)
- Hester Smith to William Penn, February 6, 1715 (Box 6, Folder 72)
- Samuel F. Smith, Elegy, undated (Box 6, Folder 73)
- Admiral Sir William Sidney Smith to Thomas Richard Underwood [in French], 1834 (Box 6, Folder 74)
- Soldiers of the Revolution, List of those buried at the 1st Presbyterian Church, undated (Box 6, Folder 75)
- B. V. Spooner to -- Spooner [brother], January 31, 1830 (Box 6, Folder 76)
- John Stanwix to Governor William Denny, July 25, 1757 (Box 6, Folder 77)
- John Stanwix to Gentlemen, July 13, 1758 (Box 6, Folder 78)
- John Stanwix to Governor William Denny, September 7, 1758 (Box 6, Folder 79)
- John Stanwix to Governor James Hamilton, March 17, 1760 (Box 6, Folder 80)
- Henry Wickham Steed to Dr. Plimmer, February 15, 1910 (Box 6, Folder 81)
- Henry Wickham Steed to Mrs. Plimmer, November 2, 1913 (Box 6, Folder 82)
- Henry Wickham Steed to Lady Frazer, December 9, 1914 (Box 6, Folder 83)
- Adam Stephen to Hugh Mercer, January 31, 1765 (Box 6, Folder 84)
- Adam Stephen to Hugh Mercer, August 10, 1765 (Box 6, Folder 85)
- Adam Stephen to Hugh Mercer, November 17, 1766 (Box 6, Folder 86)
- Adam Stephen to David Brown, July 23, 1769 (Box 6, Folder 87)
- Baron Friedrich von Steuben to Edward Hand, August 10, 1782 (Box 6, Folder 88)
- Robert H. Stewart, List of residents of Allegheny and vicinity between 1812 and 1820, undated (Box 6, Folder 89)
- Robert F. Stobo to Isaac Craig, May 7, 1872 (Box 6, Folder 90)
- Reverend Joseph Stockton, Sermon notes, undated (Box 6, Folder 91)
- Reverend Joseph Stockton to David Page, July 16, 1819 (Box 6, Folder 92)
- Jacob Strowd to Edward Hand,April 1, 1779 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Studebaker Bros. Mfg. Co. to B. L. -- & Co., January 17, 1871 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- D. B. Sturgeon to John Covode, May 20, 1863 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- W. H. Sutton to John Covode, December 17, 1859 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Hancock Taylor to William Croghan Jr., January 5, 1828 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Lorenzo Thomas to J. B. Calder, November 23, 1868 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Sir Benjamin Thompson, Count Rumford, to Messrs. Cadel & Davies, June 14, 1797 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- William Thompson to Able James, August 20, 1772 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- William Thompson to the Committee of Safety, March 16, 1776 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Francis Newton Thorpe, Typescript notes of A History of the American People, undated (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Charles Mynn Thruston Articles of agreement with John Nevill, March 28, 1774 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Alexander Tolson et al. to George W. Haller, Indentures, January 1, 1829 and February 17, 1829 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- William Townsend to Henry Phillips Jr., June 10, 1863 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- William Townsend to Henry Phillips Jr., June 29, 1863 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- William Trent to James Burd, October 4, 1755 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- William Trent to George Morgan, July 28, 1775 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- George Truitt to William Hill Wells, May 28, 1804 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Thomas Truxtun, Receipt of expenses paid by the secretary of war, April 7, 1798 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- Tryon County [N.Y.] Andries Degross vs. Amos Bennett, March 8, 1774 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- William Tryon to Sir William Johnson, June 15, 1766 (Box 7, Folder 20)
- United States 27th Congress House Committee on Revolutionary pensions, Report on petition of Betsey Vreeland, undated (Box 7, Folder 21)
- James Veech et al. to John Covode, November 17, 1860 (Box 7, Folder 22)
- Virginia, Proceedings of William Fairfax with Indian Chiefs in 1753, copies of papers held by the British Museum commissioned by William M. Darlington, undated (Box 7, Folder 23)
- Virginia Regiment, Survey of distribution of land to the regiment [duplicate], November 6, 1772 (Box 7, Folder 24)
- John Walker to David Preece Indenture, July 31, 1738 (Box 7, Folder 25)
- Thomas M. Walker to John Covode, November 20, 1869 (Box 7, Folder 26)
- Edward Ward, Deposition May 7, 1754, copies of papers held by the British Museum commissioned by William M. Darlington, undated (Box 7, Folder 27)
- Edward Ward to James Wilson, March 9, 1777 (Box 7, Folder 28)
- Samuel Warden and John Poyntz, Articles of agreement, April 29, 1815 (Box 7, Folder 29)
- Samuel Warren to W. Walker, July 31, 1847 (Box 7, Folder 30)
- L-- Washington to Mrs. Roberts (Box 7, Folder 31)
- David Thompson Watson, Uncataloged materials Alaskan Boundary case, 1903 (Box 7, Folder 32)
- David Thompson Watson, Typescript notes of Alaskan boundary case speeech, February 16, 1912 (Box 7, Folder 33)
- William Watson, Assignment of a pew in Presbyterian Church, December 5, 1817 (Box 7, Folder 34)
- Anthony Wayne to Jacob Slough, February 12, 1793 (Box 7, Folder 35)
- Anthony Wayne to Major M. Rudolph [with undated typed transcript], March 13, 1793 (Box 7, Folder 36)
- Anthony Wayne to Francisco Luis Hector, baron de Carondelet, October 15, 1796 (Box 7, Folder 37)
- Anthony Wayne to Alexander McKee, October 22, 1796 (Box 7, Folder 38)
- Daniel Webster to Harmer Denny, March 5, 1844 (Box 7, Folder 39)
- Johann Conrad Weiser to Richard Peters, June 18, 1749 (Box 7, Folder 40)
- Johann Conrad Weiser to William Allen, October 30, 1756 (Box 7, Folder 41)
- Johann Conrad Weiser, Incomplete account of an interview with an Indian chiefNovember 10, 1756 (Box 7, Folder 42)
- Johann Conrad Weiser to Timothy Horsefield, March 26, 1758 (Box 7, Folder 43)
- Johann Conrad Weiser to Timothy Horsefield, May 3, 1760 (Box 7, Folder 44)
- Samuel Wharton to --, July 1, 1770 (Box 7, Folder 45)
- William Whetten to William Croghan Jr., March 5, 1842 (Box 7, Folder 46)
- William Whetten to Dr. William Addison, June 18, 1842 (Box 7, Folder 47)
- William Wilkin, Deposition, April 24, 1783 (Box 7, Folder 48)
- John Wilkins to --, undated (Box 7, Folder 49)
- John Wilkins, Biographical sketch, undated (Box 7, Folder 50)
- John Wilkins to George Morgan, January 30, 1769 (Box 7, Folder 51)
- John Williams to Stephen Williams, October 20, 1709 (Box 7, Folder 52)
- Rufus Williams, Authorization by Thomas Mifflin for the surveyal of landAugust 13, 1792 (Box 7, Folder 53)
- Aaron Wills, Paper giving up rights to Weeping Plantation [duplicate], undated (Box 7, Folder 54)
- Henry Wilmot to --, Returns of state line surveys [copies], June 2, 1768 (Box 7, Folder 55)
- P. Wilson to William Croghan, September 23, 1821 (Box 7, Folder 56)
- John Wood to John Covode, July 29, 1861 (Box 7, Folder 57)
- John P. Wyllys to John Armstrong, April 29, 1786 (Box 7, Folder 58)
- Alshouse, Henry. Land Grant, undated (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Appointment of M.I. Magee, 1818 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Appointment of M.I. Magee, 1818 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Carlin, Wesley Indenture, 1826 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Duquesne College Application for a Charter, August 12, 1843 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Fitch, John, Articles of Argreement, March 16, 1791 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- King George I of England, Document [vellum], 1717 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Guerierre U.S. Frigate, undated (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Illinois Land Commission Indenture, April 8, 1789 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- James Biddle to the Freeholders, 1765 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Land patent to Robert Morris(copy), 1794 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Nicholas Watson letter, February 2, 1822 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Nicholas Watson letter, March 12,1826 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Pennsylvania Land Grant to Robert Morris and John Nicholson, 1794 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Pennsylvania Supreme Executive Council Grant to Robert Gordon, 1787 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- William Potter, Bill to Daniel Hartt, 1745-1746 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- Virginia Court Record, Charles City, February 4, 1680 (Box 8, Folder 17)
- George Washington, Order of the Cincinnati, undated (Box 8, Folder 18)
- J. Wilkins, Muster roll, Allegheny County militia, June - July 1794 (Box 8, Folder 19)
- J. Wilkins, Muster roll, Allegheny County militia, Handwritten copy, June - July 1794 (Box 8, Folder 20)
- Wilkinson Papers, U.S. Army Morning Report, undated (Box 8, Folder 21)
- William Butler to Thomas Bowers, March 10, 1785 (Box 8, Folder 22)
- U.S. Continental Congress Appointment, signed by John Hancock, 1775 (Box 8, Folder 23)
- U.S. Department of State Passport for David Thompson Watson, June 14, 1907 (Box 8, Folder 24)
- U.S. War Department appointment of Thomas Harrison, February 1, 1815 (Box 8, Folder 25)
- U.S. Continental Army Five Muster Rolls, 1776-1780 (Box 8, Folder 26)
- Indian Thoroughfares of Ohio, undated (Box 8, Folder 27)
- Our National Domain, undated (Box 8, Folder 28)
- Margaret Froyley, Indenture, 1723 (Box 8, Folder 29)
- John Hills, Sketch of the Suprise of German Town, undated (Oversize 1)
- John Hills, Plan of the attack of the Forts Clinton and Montgomery, undated (Oversize 2)
- Plan of Fort Ligonier [with photostats], undated (Oversize 3)
- U.S. Army Two Muster Rolls, 1864 (Oversize 4)
- William Faden, Battle of Brandywine, undated (Oversize 5)
- Belvedere Shipping Articles, undated (Oversize 6)